Guide to the Tom Davis papers, 1994-2008
George Mason University Libraries
- Tom Davis papers, 1994-2008
  - Constituent mail, Clear the Air cards, August 1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July 1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - FY00 Appropriations Language, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Press, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - School-related GSA (General Services Administration) clean-up information, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - A Failure of Initiative: Final Report of the Select Bipartisan Committee to Investigate the Preparation for and Response to Hurricane Katrina, February 15, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - GSA (General Services Administration) Warehouse Proposal, February 27, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - National Guard Youth Challenge letter, May 19, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Voting Rights Bill, March 6, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Iraq Surge, February 14, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - VDOT (Virginia Department of Transportation) Bridge letter, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Techway, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Aviation, U.S. Air, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 3 Mr. Davis name plates in envelope marked Inside Mail, Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July 29-31, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, 35643 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Clear the Air, The Clean Air Act, July 1997 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, November 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding military and tax issues, July-August 1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding USAID (United States Agency for International Development), NAFTA (North American Free Trade Agreement), EPA (Environmental Protection Agency), July-August 1997 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, and the Clean Air Act, 35612 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, August 5-7, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Puerto Rico, and air pollution, August 6-7, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Constituent mail cards regarding Live by the Law campaign, and the Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund, Circa 1997 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Baby K information (bioethics), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Crime: U.S. Park Police, August 25, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Crime: D.C. Crime, June 1995 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Crime: Law Enforcement Bill of Rights, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Government reform and oversight: Legal Services Corporation, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Black Lung, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Labor, GOP positions, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Labor miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - CRS (Congressional Research Service) report: Labor issues, 104th, January 3, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Lake Merriweather, Virginia (Water Resources Project), June 1997 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Easter Seal Society of Virginia, October-December 1995 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - TMD (Tom M. Davis) statements, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - RNC (Republican National Committee), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Director of Civilian Marksmanship (DC M), May 9, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Assault Weapons Ban, 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - COPS (Community Oriented Policing Services) program, February-July 1995 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Crime: Child pornography completed responses, March-June 1995 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Crime: GOP Crime Bill, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - H.R. 858 Federal Firefighter Pay Fairness Act, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Firefighters, June 1995 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Terrorism, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - CRS (Congressional Research Service) report: Standards of official conduct, March 10, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Seniors' Access to Continuing Care Act of 1998, August 4, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, August 1998 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Knutson-Vandenberg funds; Seniors' Access to Continuing Care Act of 1998; Food stamps for legal immigrants, August 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, August 1998 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Veteran healthcare; Patients' Bill of Rights Act of 1998, August 12, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding food stamps for legal immigrants, August 12, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Title X Public Health Services Act, August 13, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Doris Day Animal League, August 24, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July-August 1998 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Clinton child-care proposal, August 18, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding Doris Day Animal League; Food stamps for legal immigrants, the NEA (National Endowment for the Arts), August 1998 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, July-August 1998 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Tobacco Bill 107th (binder), May 3, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Tobacco harm reduction briefing book (binder), Circa 2003 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Reduction risk (light and low tar cigarettes)(binder), Circa 2003 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Baby K and Fairfax Hospital, Dateline NBC channel 4 (VHS), March 14, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Reclaiming our water: The Occoquan river watershed: A one-hour documentary (VHS), 2003 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, August 1998 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding PARCA (Patient Access to Responsible Care Act) and Equity in Prescription Insurance and Contraceptive Coverage Act of 1997, August 17-21, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hepatitis C hearing, 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - CRS (Congressional Research Service) report: Postal Reform Bill, February 15, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Anthrax hearing, March 31, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ox Road Post Office, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Vienna Post Office, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Government Reform and Oversight Committee organizational information, 105th Congress, January 1997 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - VDOT (Virginia Department of Transportation), snow removal, January 1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - SES (Senior Executive Service) pay, January 2, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - FTS (Federal Telecommunications Service Program) 2000, Post FTS2000, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Telecommuting Centers, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters, NARFE (National Active and Retired Federal Employees Association), Federal Employees Digest, Postal Workers, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - NARFE (National Active and Retired Federal Employees Association), 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - NFFE (National Federation of Federal Employees), March 1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Thrift Savings Plan, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - The Federal Diary, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Federal Workers Press, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Federal employee clippings. (from the Washington Post), February 7, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Federal employees per district, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - IRS federal employees, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Nassif building, federal workers, September 1996 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Soft landing bills and grants, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Federal Job Retraining Center in Fairfax, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Form letters, Circa 1996 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Government Service Caucus, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Government Reform and Oversight Committee, January 1997 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Civil Service Reform Bill of 1996, text and mark up (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Official Time, AFGE (American Federation of Government Employees), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Committee on Government Reform and Oversight (GROC), January 1997 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - USPS (United States Postal Service) Fairfax Station Branch at Ox Road, March 4, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - TAA (Trade Adjustment Assistance), 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Mexican trucks, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - E-Commerce / Trade, March 2003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Dreier Trade letter, May-June 2004 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Sovereign Wealth Funds, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - CNOOC (Chinese National Offshore Oil Company), 2005 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Andean FTA (Free Trade Agreement) letter, February 8, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Virginia trade (Virginia embracing globalization article in Virginia Lawyer December 2007) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Micron EX-IM (export-import), 2004-2006 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Manufacturing letter, March 16, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Panama FTA (Free Trade Agreement) letter, September 25, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Sodexo, Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - US-Singapore Free Trade Agreement (binder), circa 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Disaster Assistance, March 14, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Homeland Security / Capitol Region, February-March 2003 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - FISA (Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act), January 29, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Cargo security, May 26, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - DHS (Department of Homeland Security) Data Center, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Dogue Creek, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - C-TPAT (Customs-Trade Partnership Against Terrorism)Third Party Verification, May 26, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - CSX (railroad transportation) hazmat, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Civil Air Patrol, February-March 2007 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Biowatch / Mall, October 2005 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - ABLE DANGER, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - ADIZ (D.C. Metropolitan Area Air Defense Identification Zone), Undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - UASI (Urban Area Security Initiative), January 3, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - NCR (National Capital Region), 2005 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - COLAs (cost-of-living adjustments) and CPI (Consumer Price Index), 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Social Security, general, 1998-2001 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Supplemental Security Income (SSI), 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Social Security notch issue, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Social Security reform, July-August 2005 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 743 Social Security Protection Act, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Social Security information, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Terrorist Response Tax Exemption Act, December 2001 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Economic Stimulus Package, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Houses of Worship Tax, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Cosmetology Tax Fairness and Compliance Act of 2001 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - H.R. 1487 / AMT (alternative minimum tax) / ISO (incentive stock option), 2001 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Sale of a Primary Residence Tax, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - ESPP (employee stock purchase plans) / ISO (incentive stock options), 2002 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - R & D (Research and Development) tax credit, March 19, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Establishing America's Priorities: Writing the Nation's Budget, February 2001 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Death Tax, 107th, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Internet Taxes, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Economic Nexus, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - AMT (alternative minimum tax) Patch, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Tax cut letter, $350 billion bill, April 8, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Imputed interest, Undated (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Smithfield FSC (Foreign Sales Corporation) / ETI (Extraterritorial Income Exclusion), April 2, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - AMTax (alternative minimum tax), 2004 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Jobs Act, H.R. 4520, FSC (Foreign Sales Corporation) / ETI (Extraterritorial Income Exclusion), 2004 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - IPI (Institute for Policy Innovation) policy report (not foldered), July 2004 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Prince William County, Potomac Hospital. (brochures and pamphlets), 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Vaccines and the Autism Epidemic, Government Reform Committee, December 10, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Mercury in dental fillings, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Hemophilia, Undated (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Trauma Care Systems (Planning and Development Act), May 2002 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Alzheimer's Disease, 1998-2001 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Assisted Suicide, 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Diabetes, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Tuberculosis, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Mammograms, ACR (American College of Radiology), Josh Cooper, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Harm reduction (tobacco), 2001-2004 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Retirement security (in black folder), Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Medicare Rx, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - W & M (Committee on Ways and Means) response to SNF (skilled nursing facilities), January-February 2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - IME (Indirect Medical Education) HR response, January 8, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Alliance for Health Reform - Kaiser commission on Medicaid and the uninsured (not foldered), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - National Governors' Association (NGA) proposal, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Medicaid in Virginia, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Medicaid waivers, December 14, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - SCHIP (State Children's Health Insurance Program), September 2002 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - HCFA (Health Care Financing Administration) reform, April 4, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Medicare Fraud and Abuse, 1996, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Medicare expansion, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Medicare and choice program, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Hospice, BBA (Balanced Budget Refinements Act), 1999 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Home Health Care, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Prescription drugs, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Stem cell, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - PBOR (Patients' Bill of Rights), June-July 2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Trust for America's Health, bioterrorism preparedness, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Dietary supplements, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Medicaid, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Insurance, October 2003 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Type 2 Diabetes, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Hospice, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Racial/Ethnic Healthcare, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Kid's Health, Circa 2003 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Glaucoma Caucus, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - VA prescription challenge, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Respite Care, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Breast implants, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Physical/Occupational Therapy, July 2003 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Osteoporosis, Circa 2003 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Eyeballs, September 17, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Disabilities, Circa 2003 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Cancer, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Oncologists, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - School Nutrition, March 2003 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - HIPAA (Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act) loophole, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - H.R. 660, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Nephrology INOVA (Fairfax Hospital) Tour, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - HIV-AIDS, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Medicaid letter / Wilson, April 13, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Health Care Reform, January-February 2006 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Healthcare, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Cosigned funding letters, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Borderline personality disorder, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - MIL-SPIRIT (Impact of Integrated Mind/Body/Spirit Interventions on Military Healthcare), 2004 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - GMU (George Mason University) Health Policy Hill Day, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - H.R. 3108 Pension Funding Equity Act, October 2003 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Mad Cow, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Alzeimer's Disease information, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Tobacco, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - 110 FDA Tobacco, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence: A, 2004-2008 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: B, 2003-2007 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: C, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: D, 2005-2007 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: E, 2005-2008 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: F, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: G, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: H, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: I-J, (includes DVD), 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: K, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: L, 2003-2007 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: M, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: N, 2004-2007 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: O-Q, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: R, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: S, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: T-Z, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Tobacco Bill, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - FDA (Food and Drug Administration) Bill, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Tobacco, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - FDA Legislation in the 107th Congress (Tobacco), June 14, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - "Taking action to reduce tobacco use", Institute of Medicine National Research Council, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Star Scientific, Inc., 2002 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - "Recent developments: The role of smokeless tobacco as a reduced risk alternative to cigarette smoking", May 9, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Tobacco, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Tobacco, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Tobacco, June3, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Tobacco, June3, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Safer cigarettes, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Tobacco, 2003-2006 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Tobacco policy, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Tobacco, 2000-2003 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Tobacco, 2004-2006 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Tobacco (not foldered), 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, October 19, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, October 16 and 19, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, October 1998 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, October 1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, October 19-22, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, October 19, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, April, October, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, April, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, April, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding multiple issues, April, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - NHS (National Highway System) Bill, September 1995 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Vir bch (Virginia Beach) Pipeline, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - ICF Kaiser, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Canned (Handicapped parking; Potomac River Basin; transportation issues), 1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - National Parks; Moorefield House in Vienna; National CASU Board Meeting June 15, 1993 (not foldered), 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Colonial pipeline Congressional Hearing, May 18, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Letter regarding federal furlough; letter regarding United Taxicab Operators Association (not foldered), December 1995 and February 1, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - H.R. 1270 Yucca Mountain, April 1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - EPA (Environmental Protection Agency) Part. Regs., 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - EPA (Environmental Protection Agency) Part. Regs., 1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Job Protection Act of 1997; Healthcare (not foldered) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - DOE (Department of Energy), March 1997 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Global Warming, Fall 1996 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Department of Energy; TIA (Telecommunications Industry Association), June 1997 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - FAA (Federal Aviation Administration) Air Control FAC, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Trucks, 1993-1997 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - WW (Woodrow Wilson) Bridge insurance, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - EBA Engineering Inc, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Stupid bikes, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Woodrow Wilson Memorial Bridge, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Cars; EPA (Environmental Protection Agency); Q loans (not foldered), 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Travel agents, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence (Chip H.), 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - County of Fairfax H.R. 1463, National Capital Interest Arbitration Standards Act, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Q Funds, March 1996 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Transportation, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Holmes Run (neighborhood), 1996 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - VDOT (Virginia Department of Transportation), March 21, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Noise barriers, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Transportation issues, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - National Speed Limit. (Constituent mail) (Chip H.), 1995 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - VRE (Virginia Railway Express), transport, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Belle Haven Marina, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Department of Transportation and Related Agencies Appropriations Bill; Safe Drinking Water Act (not foldered), September 1995 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Maritime (Security Act of 1995) (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Letters regarding building a Target in Fairfax; letter regarding transportation (not foldered), 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - ISTEA (Intermodal Surface Transportation Efficiency Act of 1991), 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Q-Funds, April 29, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Airbags, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Campaign reform, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Aviation, June 1997 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Committee meetings and Congressional Hearings (multiple issues), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Think Globally, Act Locally (not foldered), October 17, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Mantua Citizens' Association oil spill, January 1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Clean Water, May 19, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Moran Tank Bill, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Trails, January 7, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Animus-La Plata, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - MFVRP (Mission Familiarization Virtual Reality Project), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - America's National Lands: The Wilderness Society, Undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - CSX & Conrail, Circa 1994 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Clean Water Amendments of 1995 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Wetlands, EPA (Environmental Protection Agency) (not foldered), 1995 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Metro Funding Panel, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Metro Hearing, July 2005 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - WMATA (Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority), 2005-2006 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Metro Police, December 2005 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Vienna Metro / Metro land use, 2003-2006 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Metro hearing, February, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Metro authorization, 2006-2007 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - WMATA (Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority), 2006 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - 110th Metro Reauthorization, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Privacy and PARP (Public Access to Records Policies) Training Manual, October 2005 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Baseball: RFK (Stadium) letter with Mayor, May 18, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Baseball: NATS (Nationals) TV, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Baseball, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Baseball: Nationals TV Hearing, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Baseball, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Metro Reauthorization, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Baseball, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Wolftrap, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Normandy Medal (includes photographs), 2001 (Box 23, Folder 4)